const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'אָהַב',
    answers: ['hij had lief', 'hij hield van'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אָמַר',
    answers: ['hij zei'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'בָּרָא',
    answers: ['hij schiep'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'הָיָה',
    answers: ['hij was', 'hij werd'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'הָלַךְ',
    answers: ['hij ging', 'hij wandelde', 'hij ging weg'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'יָדַע',
    answers: ['hij wist'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'יַחְדָּו',
    answers: ['samen', 'met elkaar', 'tegelijkertijd'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'יֶלֶד',
    answers: ['kind'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'כָּבוֹד',
    answers: ['eer', 'heerlijkheid'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'תֵּבָה',
    answers: ['ark', 'kistje', 'rieten mandje'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'עוֹד',
    answers: ['nog', 'nog steeds', 'weer', 'opniew'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'עַל־פְּנֵי',
    answers: ['over', 'overheen', 'boven'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'עַתָּה',
    answers: ['nu', 'welnu'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'פֹּה',
    answers: ['hier'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'צְבָאוֹת',
    answers: ['Sebaot', 'legers', 'heerscharen'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שַׁבָּת',
    answers: ['sabbat'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שָׁם',
    answers: ['daar'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שְׁנֵיהֶם',
    answers: ['zij tweeën', 'zij tweeen', 'alletwee', 'beide', 'beiden'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson10Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson10-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 10 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson10Vocabulary
